

CONTACT

07485 137021

Fulani07@gmail.com

https://github.com/Tijanif

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tijanifulani/

PROFILE

I am a web developer with 4 years commercial experience, from team management to sales and marketing of e-commerce platforms. I'm constantly learning new things. I love the daily challenges of web development: writing quality code, learning new technologies, and solving complex problems. I am looking for a challenging position with the opportunity to make an impact and learn on a daily basis.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS/Sass, JavaScript, React Bootstrap, Ruby on Rails

EDUCATION

- 2008 -2011 BSC INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS AND POLITICS (2:1). LONDON METROPOLITAN UNIVERSITY.
- **2011 2012** MSC INTERNATIONAL POLITICAL ECONOMY. UNIVERSITY OF KENT, BRUSSELS SCHOOL OF INTERNATIONAL STUDIES

Personal Projects

 Frontend Mentor Challenges. Built multiple sites using HTML CSS and JS.

Live site: https://blissful-montalcini-3567f2.netlify.app/

• My Book List: Vanilla JS project build using classes.

Live site: https://tijanif.github.io/myBookList/

 Travel Home: A travel webpage build with Materialise CSS.

Live site: https://tijanif.github.io/travelhome/

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PROGRAMMAI SEPT- 2019 - FEB 2020

Part of a two man team building the Programmai frontend using Javascript and React.

Working closely with the product manager to build the frontend from scratch.

Working with the backend team to make sure that data from the backend is displayed as it should.

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSE

Intensive course learning Ruby, Rails, HTML5, CSS/sass, Bootstrap, Javascript, SQL, PostgreSQL, MVC architecture, OOP, Git. GitHub and Heroku.

CUSTOMER CARE NORWAY POD POINT LTD 2018 TO 2019

Delivered the highest standards of service to new and existing clients

Help create pod-point.no by being the link between the Norway team and the development team.

Worked closely with the development team during the development of Pod-point.no.

E-BUSINESS MANAGER NORDICS COMFORTCLICK 2017 TO 2018

Designed high impact, user-centered websites-Implemented SEO and Google ads strategies for www.weightworld.no